{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059279963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059279962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059280397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059280397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059280881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059280880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059281524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059281524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059284530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059284530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059284623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059284623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059285477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059285476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059285891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059285890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059286719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059286719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059289722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059289722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059290769","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059290769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059291467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059291466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059291663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059291662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059292243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059292242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059293042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059293042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059296079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059296079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059296183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059296183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059296952","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059296952"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059297468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059297468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059297664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059297663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059298340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059298340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059301121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059301121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059301345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059301345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059302048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059302048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059305057","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059305057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059305170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059305170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059305858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059305858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059306342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059306342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059307155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059307155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059310181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059310181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059310821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059310820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059311560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059311560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059312283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059312283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059312420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059312420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059313266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059313265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059316271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059316271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059316416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059316416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059317130","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059317130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059317643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059317643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059318367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059318366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059321425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059321425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059321858","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059321858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059322351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059322351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059322474","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059322474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059323228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059323228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059326248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059326248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059326360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059326360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059327114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059327114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059327486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059327486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059328575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059328574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059331365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059331365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059331838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059331838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059332847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059332847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059335798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059335798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059335935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059335934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059336511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059336511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059336775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059336775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059337389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059337389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059340684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059340684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059341403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059341403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059341936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059341936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059342089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059342089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059342627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059342626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059342760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059342760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059343353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059343353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059346365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059346365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059346460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059346459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059347179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059347178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059347605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059347605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059348565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059348564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059351602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059351601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059351935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059351935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059352660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059352660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059352724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059352724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059353791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059353790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059355990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059355990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059356456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059356456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059358032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059358032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" NIIPENDAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059359172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059359172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059362166","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059362166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059363916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059363915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" UNAZIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059364392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059364391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059364978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059364978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059365274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059365274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059366296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059366296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059369018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059369018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059369075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059369075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 32c1a503-5fa4-48b7-9871-22f6cc2839e6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059387596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059387595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059388113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059388112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059388647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059388647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059388883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059388882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059389089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059389089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059389748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059389747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059389823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059389823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059391238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059391237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059394090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059394090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059394673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059394673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059395661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059395661"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059396064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059396064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059396983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059396983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059399560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059399560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059400003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059400003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059400676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059400676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059400962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059400962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059401077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059401077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059401688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059401688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059402746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059402746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059405694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059405694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIO"," userResponse":" SIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059405910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059405910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059406549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059406548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059407209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059407208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059407622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059407622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059408475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059408475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059411173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059411173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059411629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059411628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059412163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059412162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059412409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059412408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059412645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059412645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059413591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059413591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJANO"," userResponse":" NJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059416562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059416562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059417248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059417248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIVU"," userResponse":" MBIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059417543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059417543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059417847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059417847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059418525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059418525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJANO"," userResponse":" NJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059420884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059420884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059421487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059421487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBICHI"," userResponse":" MBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059421742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059421742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059422027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059422027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059422781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059422780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059423846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059423846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059426498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059426497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059426975","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059426975"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059427889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059427889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAVULI"," userResponse":" MIAVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059428105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059428104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059429143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059429143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEUSI"," userResponse":" MIEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059432313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059432313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAVULI"," userResponse":" MIAVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059432957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059432957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059433313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059433313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059434184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059434184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEUSI"," userResponse":" MIEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059436917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059436916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059437390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059437389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059437944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059437944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAMU"," userResponse":" DAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059438071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059438070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059439240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059439240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059442106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059442105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059442885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059442885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADINI"," userResponse":" MADINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059443410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059443409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059444095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059444095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAMU"," userResponse":" DAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059447175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059447174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAIFANYA"," userResponse":" YANAIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059447799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059447798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAMU"," userResponse":" DAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059448281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059448280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059449200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059449200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059451777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059451776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059452278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059452277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059452906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059452905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059453159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059453158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059454158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059454157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059456926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059456924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059457047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059457047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" a80001cb-27f8-4b4a-afcf-4c0ab22d3e58"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059468787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059468787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 3c9d74e8-0fae-434c-a7f6-4940a416a934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059471855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059471855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 3c9d74e8-0fae-434c-a7f6-4940a416a934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-I-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059475131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059475131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 3c9d74e8-0fae-434c-a7f6-4940a416a934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-U-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059478208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059478208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 3c9d74e8-0fae-434c-a7f6-4940a416a934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-E-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059481261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059481261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 3c9d74e8-0fae-434c-a7f6-4940a416a934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059486993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059486991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 3c9d74e8-0fae-434c-a7f6-4940a416a934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059516630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059516630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 239a4985-6b2e-48b5-b148-b3ebdf3c59c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-8-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059524704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059524704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 239a4985-6b2e-48b5-b148-b3ebdf3c59c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-0-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059531827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059531827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 239a4985-6b2e-48b5-b148-b3ebdf3c59c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-0-1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059537240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059537240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 239a4985-6b2e-48b5-b148-b3ebdf3c59c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-3-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059542763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059542763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 239a4985-6b2e-48b5-b148-b3ebdf3c59c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548059550350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548059550350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190121_112706"," gameId":" 239a4985-6b2e-48b5-b148-b3ebdf3c59c5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-7-8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}